

SULTANOVA ANAHIT Front-end web developer

CONTACTS

in LinkedIn

Portfolio

(+374 77) 42-18-86

Sultanova.anahit92@gmail.com

SKILLS

- ✓ HTML / HTML5, CSS / CSS3
- ✓ Sass, Less, Bootstrap
- ✓ JavaScript (ES5, ES6), jQuery
- ✓ React JS
- ✔ PHP, MySQL
- ✓ Wordpress, Joomla
- ✔ Photoshop, Figma
- ✓ Agile methodology such as Scrum; Jira, Trello
- ✓ Git.
- ✓ Windows OS, Linux OS

LANGUAGES

- ✓ English / B1 Intermediate
- ✓ Armenian / Native
- ✓ Russian / Native

EDUCATION

State Engineering University of Armenia (SEUA)

Computer Systems and Informatics (Information Technologies and Automation) / Bachelor degree Sep 2009 - May 2013

'Optimum' IT Education Center

Web Technologies (HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, WordPress) Sep 2013 - May 2014

OVERVIEW

Web developer with 7+ years experience.

I have experience in web site design, building, testing and customization. Worked with WordPress, developed plugins, themes and created sites. Want to work with JavaScript and React JS, create beautiful and innovate websites and applications.

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer

Apr 2022 - Aug 2022 · 4m

Changing and improving of existing platform functionality, development web sites frontend, bug fixes, adding the new features.

♥ Betinspire

Full Stack Developer

Aug 2020 - Jan 2022 · 1y 6m

Managing time-sensitive updates, including content changes, bug fixes, adding the new features.

9 10web

Tech Support specialist / Team Lead

Dec 2017 - Aug 2019 · 1y 9m

- * Provided technical support for over 50+ Premium Plugins and Extensions.
- * Provided professional customer service, managing 20+ tickets and email requests a day.
- * Lead and managed a team of 4 junior developers.
- **♀**10web

Teacher of Web Technologies

Oct 2015 - Jun 2016 · 9m

- * Taught HTML, CSS and 'Javascript for beginners'.
- * Developed documentations and slides to teach mentioned technologies.
- 'Optimum' IT Education center

Full Stack Engineer

Jun 2014 - Dec 2017 · 3y 7m

- * Developed and modified themes and plugins for WordPress and and Joomla CMS.
- * Designed, coded and modified 10+ web sites based on Wordpress and Joomla.
- * Have experience of optimizing, improving, debugging live websites.
- **♥** WebDorado

Software testing manager

Dec 2013 - Apr 2014 · 5m

- * Monitored, created and populated QA sheets with designers and managers.
- * Provided trainings for continues documents automatization in Register Offices over the Yerevan.
- **♀** VXSoft